Bryce Quintana

Glendora, CA

Email: musicmaker773@gmail.com Github: https://github.com/musicmaker773

Portfolio: https://musicmaker773.github.io/portfolio

Profile:

Has recently graduated from Cal Poly Pomona with a Bachelor's of Computer Science and a 3.69 GPA (Magna Cum Laude). Is willing to work to gain enough experience for a stable senior position. Is hardworking and willing to learn anything new on the go.

Education:

California Polytechnic University, Pomona Bachelor's of Science: Computer Science, 2020 3.69 GPA (with Magna Cum Laude)

Citrus College

Associates of Science for Transfer: Mathematics, 2018

3.6 GPA

Skills:

Programming Languages: C/C++, Java (Command Line and GUI), C#, Python, Go, PHP, HTML/5, CSS/3, Javascript (Vanilla, React, and Angular), SQL (with MySQL and SQLite), and XML

Operating Systems: Windows, Mac OS, Linux

IDEs: Intellij, PyCharm, Visual Studio, Brackets, Android Studio, MacOS Terminal, and Windows Terminal Miscellaneous: Data Structures, Socket Programming (TCP/IP and UDP), Multithreading (with Thread Pools), HTTP request handling, Google Drive, Microsoft Office, and Wordpress

Projects:

Coronavirus Appointment Scheduler Website Server

Position: Project Manager/Developer

Concept: Building a website that is locally run by a server and schedules, reschedules, and cancels appointments. Handles many requests with multithreading.

- Built a Server from scratch with C that handled HTTP requests and responded with website pages.
- Build the website pages with HTML, CSS, and Javascript.

Android Therapy Chatbot

Position: Developer

Concept: Create a mobile app on Android Studio that is a chatbot for therapy. It will connect to a running server.

- Build the frontend with XML and backend with Java.
- Connect to a running server with a REST API and format data with JSON.

Coronavirus Case Predictor

Position: Individual Project

Concept: Create a Neural Network that predicts future COVID-19 cases.

- Coded it in Python with Numpy and Pandas.
- Use previous data and predict ten days ahead the number of cases.

Activities:

Game Development Club

Participant

September 2019 - December 2019

- Compete in a game jam by developing a game within three months with a group.
- Attend meetings and workshops that discuss game dev related terms and knowledge of the job field.

Work Experience:

Uber Eats:

Delivery Driver September 2018 - Present

Deliver food to proper destination

Pizza Hut:

Delivery Driver

November 2016 - April 2018

- Deliver Pizza to proper destination
- Miscellaneous (i.e. Wash Dishes, Cleaning, Cutting Pizza, Preparing, etc.)